(Sheldon:)Would you like to hear
another reason
(Sheldon:)why men are
better than women?
(Leonard:)Sure, let's make it
an even hundred.
(Sheldon:)You would never kiss me
and make me say "I love you"
(Sheldon:)and then break up with me.
(Penny:)I wouldn't.
(Sheldon:)And you know why?
'Cause you're a man.
(Sheldon:)The champagne of genders.
(Leonard:)Well, I may be a man,
(Leonard:)but I think I'm the one
that screwed up on this one.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, well, and you admit it,
like a man.
(Sheldon:)All you hear
women say is,
"I'll just have a salad."
You know?
"Where's my lip gloss?"
"I think this element
should be called radium."
(Sheldon:)That last one was Madame Curie.
(Leonard:)I figured that out.
(Leonard:)You know what?
She was kind of an honorary man.
(Sheldon:)She had a penis made of science.
(Leonard:)Can't believe I'm spending
my wedding night with you.
(Raj:)Really?
(Sheldon:)I never imagined it
any other way.